Tuvalu, the fourth smallest nation in the world, announced its intention to become the world's first digital country back in 2022.
图瓦卢，世界第四小的国家，早在2022年就宣布了要成为世界上第一个数字国家的意图。
But why, and how?
但原因是什么，又该如何实现呢？
Facing the devastating effects of rising sea levels caused by climate change, the nation, made up of three reef islands and six atolls, is rapidly becoming uninhabitable.
面对气候变化导致的海平面上升带来的毁灭性影响，这个由三个礁岛和六个环礁组成的国家正迅速变得不适宜居住。
Tuvalu sits between Hawaii and Australia and is grappling with increasingly dire conditions.
图瓦卢位于夏威夷和澳大利亚之间，正在努力应对日益严峻的状况。
In 2022, at high tide, nearly 40% of the capital became submerged, according to the news agency Reuters.
据路透社报道，2022年涨潮时，首都近40%的地区被淹没。
A recent assessment by scientists at NASA indicated that "much of the land plus critical infrastructure will sit below the level of the current high tide by 2050".
美国宇航局科学家最近的一项评估表明，"到2050年，大部分土地以及关键基础设施将位于当前涨潮水位以下"。
And projections suggest the entire country could be underwater by the year 2100.
预测显示，到2100年，整个国家可能被海水淹没。
Global warming has already displaced many of Tuvalu's 11,000 inhabitants, while coral bleaching and coastal erosion continue to degrade the surrounding environment.
全球变暖已经导致图瓦卢11,000名居民中的许多人流离失所，而珊瑚白化和海岸侵蚀仍在继续破坏周边环境。
This is why the government plans to back up the country and rebuild a virtual online replica.
这就是为什么政府计划备份整个国家，并重建一个虚拟的在线复制品。
The announcement was first made at the UN Climate Change Conference, COP27 by Tuvalu's Minister of Justice, Simon Kofe.
这一声明首先由图瓦卢司法部长西蒙·科菲在联合国气候变化大会COP27上宣布。
He said, "As our land slips below the ocean, we have no choice but to become the world's first digital nation.
他说："随着我们的土地滑入海洋，我们别无选择，只能成为世界上第一个数字国家。
Our land, our ocean, our culture are the most precious assets of our people".
我们的土地、海洋、文化是我们人民最宝贵的资产。"
The country has since been preserving Tuvalu's cultural and historical identity by recording historical documents, maps, family photograph albums, traditional songs, and other cultural practices, all of which will be accessible online.
自那以后，该国一直在通过记录历史文献、地图、家庭相册、传统歌曲和其他文化习俗来保护图瓦卢的文化和历史特性，所有这些都将可以在线访问。
In early 2024, Place, a global non-profit organisation, began mapping the physical features of Funafuti, Tuvalu's capital, using drones and 360-degree cameras.
2024年初，全球非营利组织Place开始使用无人机和360度摄像机绘制图瓦卢首都富纳富提的物理特征。
Though moving a country online has legal challenges – international law requires a country to have territory and population, both of which are uncertain in Tuvalu's future.
尽管将一个国家转移到线上存在法律挑战——国际法要求一个国家拥有领土和人口，而这两者在图瓦卢的未来都是不确定的。
At the same time, critics argue the plan is just for publicity, highlighting the need to reduce emissions.
同时，批评者认为该计划只是为了宣传，强调需要减少排放。
Whatever happens, a digital twin of the country will help preserve its culture and heritage for generations to come.
无论发生什么，该国的数字孪生体都将有助于为后代保护其文化和遗产。